(Howard:)That's the estrogen hat trick.
(Leonard:)What it is is a cacophonous assault of
eucalyptus, bayberry, cinnamon and vanilla.
(Leonard:)It's as if my head were trapped
in the pajamas of a sultan.
(Raj:)Sheldon, if you don't like this stuff,
let's just go next door and build her a bear.
(Sheldon:)I told you before, bears are terrifying.
(Howard:)Come on, bath stuff. It's perfect.
(Howard:)You got a scented candle,
a cleansing buff.
Spearmint-and-green-tea-scented bath oil
promotes relaxation.
(Sheldon:)That presupposes Penny is tense.
(Raj:)She knows you. She's tense.
We all are. Buy a basket.
- Excuse me, we're ready.
- No, we're not.
(Sheldon:)Let's say for a moment that
I accept the bath-item-gift hypothesis.
(Sheldon:)I now lay the following conundrum
at your feet. Which size?
(Howard:)This one. Let's go.
- You put no thought into that.
- I'm sorry. Ah...
(Howard:)This one. Let's go.
(Sheldon:)I have insufficient data to proceed.
(Sheldon:)- Excuse me, miss?
- Yes?